{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025465134","data":{"timestamp":" 947025465134"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 4452864c-35e5-4e0d-a965-936d7947169a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025474157","data":{"timestamp":" 947025474157"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 4452864c-35e5-4e0d-a965-936d7947169a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025485832","data":{"timestamp":" 947025485832"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 4452864c-35e5-4e0d-a965-936d7947169a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025499161","data":{"timestamp":" 947025499161"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 4452864c-35e5-4e0d-a965-936d7947169a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025503653","data":{"timestamp":" 947025503653"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 4452864c-35e5-4e0d-a965-936d7947169a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025516273","data":{"timestamp":" 947025516273"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 4452864c-35e5-4e0d-a965-936d7947169a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025522730","data":{"timestamp":" 947025522729"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 4452864c-35e5-4e0d-a965-936d7947169a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025534620","data":{"timestamp":" 947025534620"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 4452864c-35e5-4e0d-a965-936d7947169a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025537418","data":{"timestamp":" 947025537418"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 4452864c-35e5-4e0d-a965-936d7947169a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025545161","data":{"timestamp":" 947025545161"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 4452864c-35e5-4e0d-a965-936d7947169a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025554894","data":{"timestamp":" 947025554894"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 4452864c-35e5-4e0d-a965-936d7947169a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025566415","data":{"timestamp":" 947025566415"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 4452864c-35e5-4e0d-a965-936d7947169a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025576123","data":{"timestamp":" 947025576122"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 4452864c-35e5-4e0d-a965-936d7947169a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025586751","data":{"timestamp":" 947025586751"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 4452864c-35e5-4e0d-a965-936d7947169a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025600254","data":{"timestamp":" 947025600254"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 4452864c-35e5-4e0d-a965-936d7947169a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025612350","data":{"timestamp":" 947025612350"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 4452864c-35e5-4e0d-a965-936d7947169a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025626011","data":{"timestamp":" 947025626011"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 4452864c-35e5-4e0d-a965-936d7947169a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025636009","data":{"timestamp":" 947025636009"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 4452864c-35e5-4e0d-a965-936d7947169a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025639530","data":{"timestamp":" 947025639530"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 4452864c-35e5-4e0d-a965-936d7947169a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025646647","data":{"timestamp":" 947025646647"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 4452864c-35e5-4e0d-a965-936d7947169a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025656405","data":{"timestamp":" 947025656405"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 4452864c-35e5-4e0d-a965-936d7947169a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025670545","data":{"timestamp":" 947025670545"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 4452864c-35e5-4e0d-a965-936d7947169a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025676037","data":{"timestamp":" 947025676037"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 4452864c-35e5-4e0d-a965-936d7947169a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025686138","data":{"timestamp":" 947025686138"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 4452864c-35e5-4e0d-a965-936d7947169a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025692823","data":{"timestamp":" 947025692823"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 4452864c-35e5-4e0d-a965-936d7947169a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" c"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025699601","data":{"timestamp":" 947025699601"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 4452864c-35e5-4e0d-a965-936d7947169a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025711472","data":{"timestamp":" 947025711472"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 4452864c-35e5-4e0d-a965-936d7947169a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025720779","data":{"timestamp":" 947025720779"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 4452864c-35e5-4e0d-a965-936d7947169a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025743133","data":{"timestamp":" 947025743133"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 4452864c-35e5-4e0d-a965-936d7947169a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025760255","data":{"timestamp":" 947025760255"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 4452864c-35e5-4e0d-a965-936d7947169a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025768482","data":{"timestamp":" 947025768482"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 4452864c-35e5-4e0d-a965-936d7947169a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025777027","data":{"timestamp":" 947025777027"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 4452864c-35e5-4e0d-a965-936d7947169a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025781772","data":{"timestamp":" 947025781771"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 4452864c-35e5-4e0d-a965-936d7947169a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025797317","data":{"timestamp":" 947025797316"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 4452864c-35e5-4e0d-a965-936d7947169a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025810219","data":{"timestamp":" 947025810219"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 4452864c-35e5-4e0d-a965-936d7947169a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025813362","data":{"timestamp":" 947025813361"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 4452864c-35e5-4e0d-a965-936d7947169a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.si.rand.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025825718","data":{"timestamp":" 947025825717"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 8cada5b0-11aa-400e-8ab7-b6dd19243944"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.si.rand.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" siyo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIYO"," userResponse":" SIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.si.rand.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025826775","data":{"timestamp":" 947025826774"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 8cada5b0-11aa-400e-8ab7-b6dd19243944"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.si.rand.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" siyo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIYO"," userResponse":" SIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.si.rand.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025832390","data":{"timestamp":" 947025832389"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 8cada5b0-11aa-400e-8ab7-b6dd19243944"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.si.rand.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sita"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" SITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.si.rand.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025833473","data":{"timestamp":" 947025833472"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 8cada5b0-11aa-400e-8ab7-b6dd19243944"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.si.rand.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sita"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" SITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.si.rand.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025837536","data":{"timestamp":" 947025837536"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 8cada5b0-11aa-400e-8ab7-b6dd19243944"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.si.rand.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SIMO"," userResponse":" START_SIMO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.si.rand.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025838591","data":{"timestamp":" 947025838591"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 8cada5b0-11aa-400e-8ab7-b6dd19243944"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.si.rand.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMO"," userResponse":" SIMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.si.rand.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025839653","data":{"timestamp":" 947025839653"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 8cada5b0-11aa-400e-8ab7-b6dd19243944"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.si.rand.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMO"," userResponse":" SIMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.si.rand.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025844261","data":{"timestamp":" 947025844261"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 8cada5b0-11aa-400e-8ab7-b6dd19243944"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.si.rand.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" siri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIRI"," userResponse":" SIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.si.rand.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025845319","data":{"timestamp":" 947025845318"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 8cada5b0-11aa-400e-8ab7-b6dd19243944"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.si.rand.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" siri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIRI"," userResponse":" SIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.si.rand.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025851196","data":{"timestamp":" 947025851196"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 8cada5b0-11aa-400e-8ab7-b6dd19243944"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.si.rand.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sina"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SINA"," userResponse":" SINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.si.rand.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025852267","data":{"timestamp":" 947025852266"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 8cada5b0-11aa-400e-8ab7-b6dd19243944"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.si.rand.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sina"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SINA"," userResponse":" SINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.si.rand.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025856286","data":{"timestamp":" 947025856285"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 8cada5b0-11aa-400e-8ab7-b6dd19243944"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.si.rand.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISA"," userResponse":" SISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.si.rand.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025857353","data":{"timestamp":" 947025857353"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 8cada5b0-11aa-400e-8ab7-b6dd19243944"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.si.rand.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISA"," userResponse":" SISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.si.rand.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025861878","data":{"timestamp":" 947025861877"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 8cada5b0-11aa-400e-8ab7-b6dd19243944"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.si.rand.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sifa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIFA"," userResponse":" SIFA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.si.rand.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025862961","data":{"timestamp":" 947025862960"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 8cada5b0-11aa-400e-8ab7-b6dd19243944"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.si.rand.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sifa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIFA"," userResponse":" SIFA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.si.rand.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025867447","data":{"timestamp":" 947025867447"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 8cada5b0-11aa-400e-8ab7-b6dd19243944"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.si.rand.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" siku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.si.rand.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025868491","data":{"timestamp":" 947025868491"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 8cada5b0-11aa-400e-8ab7-b6dd19243944"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.si.rand.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" siku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.si.rand.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025873581","data":{"timestamp":" 947025873580"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 8cada5b0-11aa-400e-8ab7-b6dd19243944"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.si.rand.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.si.rand.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025874650","data":{"timestamp":" 947025874650"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 8cada5b0-11aa-400e-8ab7-b6dd19243944"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.si.rand.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.si.rand.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025879470","data":{"timestamp":" 947025879469"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 8cada5b0-11aa-400e-8ab7-b6dd19243944"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.si.rand.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISI"," userResponse":" SISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.si.rand.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025880510","data":{"timestamp":" 947025880509"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 8cada5b0-11aa-400e-8ab7-b6dd19243944"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.si.rand.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISI"," userResponse":" SISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.si.rand.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025884093","data":{"timestamp":" 947025884091"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 8cada5b0-11aa-400e-8ab7-b6dd19243944"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.si.rand.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" sisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947025884188","data":{"timestamp":" 947025884188"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_013714"," gameId":" 8cada5b0-11aa-400e-8ab7-b6dd19243944"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.si.rand.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISI"," userResponse":" SISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}